Guide to the John N. Warfield papers, 1931-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Textual Materials, 1943-2001; (51 boxes)
  - "Photographs: Demosophia in use at George Mason University," Fairfax, VA, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - "Photographs: Southwest Fisheries Center (SWFC) Interactive Management Workshop," LA Jolla, CA, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: The Mathematics of Structure," Lecture #4, [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Metrics of Complexity," Lecture #5, [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable Thought Leaders on Second - Order Thought (Thought About Thought)," Lecture #7, [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Infrastructure for the Work Program of Complexity," Lecture #9, [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Why Johnny Cannot Design Software," Lecture # 10 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Managerial Self - Delusion via Killer Assumptions," Lecture #13 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Structuring Discursivity for the Domain of Complexity," Lecture #14 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Process Leadership in Organization," Video Lecture #1 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Abstracts of Powerpoint Presentations," [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Process Leadership in Organizations," Lecture #1 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Interactive Management Process Leaders in Organizations," Lecture #2 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - "Managing the Unmanageable: Thought Leaders on Behavioral Pathologies," Lecture #3 [John N. Warfield], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - "All Files Report (2001 Revised Edition)," [John N. Warfield], January 22, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - "The Work Program of Complexity: Resolving Complexity Cooperatively," [John N. Warfield], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - "Vertical Incoherence in Three Level Organizations," Presented at UKSS Conference, U.K., July 9, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "Two Domain Theory of Action: Stept Toward Meeting the Demands of Complexity," [John N. Warfield], Mat 19, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - "Overview John N. Warfield's 30-Year Research Program on Complexity," [John N. Warfield], August 28, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - "Patterns & Behavior," [John N. Warfield], January 1998 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - "A Prose-Graphics Glossary of Complexity," Draft #1 for Review [John N. Warfield], February 28, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - "Transparencies for the MAthematics of Structure," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - "Warfield's Organization of Literature," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - "What Questions Have Been Formulated & Answered in a 30-Year Research Program to Study Complexity?," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - "Complexity Implications," Presented at the Program on Peacekeeping Policy Workshop, Arlington, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Categories of Topics of "A Science of Complexity," Bibliography [John N. Warfield], January 27, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - "Discovery & Complexity: A Small Anthology of Problematiques & Interpretations," [John N. Warfield], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - "Enhancing Understanding in the Domain of Complexity Through a Model Exchange Strategy," [John N. Warfield], August 5, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - "The Evolution of Thought about Thought, From Aristotle to Focault," Presented at Washington D.C.[John N. Warfield], August 22, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - "An Example IM Workshop Place,1999 (IM Workshop Prototype Plan)," [John N. Warfield, Staley Scott] (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - "Four Funerals & A Wedding or how the Grinch Stole Science (Cellpack)," [John N. Warfield], September 1, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - "Institute for Advanced Study in the Integrative Sciences - IASIS, Newsletter #1, 2 & 3, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - "Marketing Information for: A Structure Based Science of Complexity," [John N. Warfield], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - "Problematique (1999): Evolution of an Idea," [John N. Warfield, George H.Perino) (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - "Programmed Instructions Units: Excerpts from Designs of Future of Environmental Education," Final Report, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - "Prose - Graphics Outline of Science of Complexity (Cellpack)," [John N. Warfield], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - "A Role for Formalism in Integrative Studies," [John N. Warfield, Rosamond Warfield], 1999 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - "The Science of Complexity & How it Translates into Interactive Management Work," Presented at Ford Motor Company, Essex, U.K., July 7, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - "Short Presentation on the work of Mrs.Carol Jeffrey in Liberia who was Using Interactive Management," Presented at Cosmos Club,Washington D.C., April 27, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - "Twenty Laws of Complexity (1999): Science Application in Organizations," [John N. Warfield], January 1999 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - "Why Johnny Can't Design Software," IEEE Presentation Lexington Park, MD [John N. Warfield], April 24, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - "The Work Program of Complexity," Presented Via Picture-tell to ITESM, April 13, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - "An Effective Approach to Manage Complexity of Organizations: The Structure - Based Science of Complexity," [John N. Warfield, Xuefeng Song], March 2000 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - "The Comparison Among these Schools of Science of Complexity," [John N. Warfield, Song Xuefeng], August 2000 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - "Lowering Cultural Barriers to Fast Cycle Time," Ford Motor Company [Robert G.Delosh], February 4, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Apt Workshop #5 & Other Correspondence," [Staley Scott] Ford Motor Company, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Ford Motor Company: Apt Task Parameter Development," Ford Motor Company, June 15, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Overview Report Issued by Ford Motor Company", June 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Rapid Response Manufacturing (RRM) General Design Process Preliminary Draft of Final Report", March 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "IDEF Project & Blackboard: Technical Papers Sent by Scoot Staley," Ford Motor Company, September 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "Rapid Response Manufacturing (RRM) Workshop #2 & Other Papers on Planning," Ford Motor Company, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "World Class CLN Total Program Work Plan", 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Correspondence with Robert Delosh on Saudi Book & Workplan Structure," Ford Motor Company, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "An Introduction to Feature Theory: Ford Motor Company", 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Ford 1992, APT Workshop & Planning Notes & Correspondents (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Old Ford Vax Files, Correspondence With Scott Staley," Ford Motor Company, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "First Unsorted/PIM/PDM Session Culture & Other Correspondence," [Scott Staley], 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - CDD - Direct Engineering Workshop," Ford Motor Company, June 30, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "News Clipping on Transue & Hagenlocker," Ford Motor Company, June 26, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "Blackboaord Approach to Integration of Crankshaft Analysis & Applications," [D. Fagan], 1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Rapid Response Manufacturing (RRM) Steering Group Meeting," Ford Motor Company, March 1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "Correspondence Between John N. Warfield & Scott, Staley," Ford Motor Company, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Theory & Practise of Model Management Proposal to Ford Motor Company ", September 1994 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Ford Interactive Management Workshop #1 & 2", 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Ford Interactive Management Workshop #1 & 2", 1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Ford Interactive Management Workshop #1 & 2", 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "Ford Interactive Management Workshop," Workshop Directory Loaded by Benjamin Broome, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Documents Related to Ford Workshop: Summary Report", 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Ford Analytical Powertrain Workshops," Working Papers, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Ford Analytical Powertrain Workshops," Working Papers, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - "Ford Rapid Response Manufacturing (RRM) Workshops," Working Papers, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - "Ford Rapid Response Manufacturing (RRM) Workshops," Working Papers, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Product Information Management (PIM) at Ford Motor Company", 1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - "Transfer of Interactive Management Technology to Ford Motor Company," Ford Final Project Report[John N. Warfield], 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - "Newspapers Clippings Concerned With Ford Motor, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "Ford Workshops 92 & Miscellaneous References Working Papers", 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "Ford Workshops 92 & Miscellaneous References Working Papers", 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - "Universal Priers to Science: Draft #1," [John N. Warfield], January 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Universal Priers to Science: How the Liberal Arts Could Revitalize Science," Presented at ETA, Texas [John N. Warfield], October 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "National Center for Sociotechnical System Research & Design: A Proposal to National Science Foundation (NSF)," [John N. Warfield, Ralph Winder, Alexander Christakis], January 15, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "The Magical Three -- Plus or Minus Zero," Presented at International Conference of Society for General Systems Research, Budapest, Hungary, June 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "List of Manuscript Ideas," [John N. Warfield], February 1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Institutes & Centers in the Interactive University," Draft [John N. Warfield], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "On the Design of Language for System Design," Slides for Presentation in Vienna [John N. Warfield], April 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - "Preface to the Chinese Edition of Societal Systems: Planning, Policy & Complexity," [John N. Warfield], January 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Structural Analysis & A Complexity Metric for High - Level Software Languages," Kyoto, Japan[John N. Warfield, Ohuchi,Azuma, Kaki Ikuo], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - "Technomyopia Threatens our National Security," Task Report [John N. Warfield], June 22, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - "Center for Interactive Management (CIM) Archives: Copied from GMU Vax in 1991 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "Conclusions of an Independent Observer," In Final Report on Improving Smart Munitions Acquisition Management, Washington D.C., February 1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - "Design Science: Experience in Teaching Large System Design," [John N. Warfield], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "Design Systems: Generic Theory & Methodology," [John N. Warfield, A.N. Christakis, David Keever], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "Designing the Great University," Draft [John N. Warfield], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "Editorial Procedures for Systems Research," an Editorial [Rosamond Warfield], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - "Findings & Recommendations for the Continuing Development of Ghana," Board Csir, Accra,Ghana, January 1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "Foundations of Conceptual Science," [John N. Warfield], April 11, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - "The Great University: A Seminar Series," George Mason University, Virginia, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - "Papers Which Predated George Mason University Seminar in 1989 on the Great University," Five Phases of Growth by Greiner, 1984-1989 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #6," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #5," [John N. Warfield], March 7, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #4," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #3," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #2," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - "The Great University - Typed Transcripts for Seminar #1," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - "Outlines of Four Seminars, in the Great University Seminar Series," [John N. Warfield], February 1990 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - "Success Bundle for Systems Science Program", June 8, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - "Sociotechnical Modeling for Development Nations," [John N. Warfield,Moses N.B.Ayiku], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - "Simple Systems Models Based on Sophisticated Assumptions," Published in Polish Journal [John N. Warfield], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - "Nexus the Newsletter of the Center for Interactive Management", undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - "The management of Complexity Through Systems Design: A Seminar Workshop," Presented at ITESM, Mexico, December 1989 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - "Interpretive Structural Modeling (ISM) History More or Less," [Rosamond Warfield], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - "Arizona System," Bankrolled by IBM, University of Arizona, UCSON [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - "Center for Interactive Management Reports, List of Contents", 1990 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - "Cybernetics, System Science & the Great University System Research," [John N. Warfield], April 1990 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - "Economics & Systems Science," Presented at World Conference, New York City., June 15, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - "Decision Support Center REquirements," Presented to Faculty/staff of DSMC, Ft. Belvoir, VA, September 5, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - "Generic Panning: Research Results & Applications," [John N. Warfield), 1990 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - "Generic Systems Design & Interactive Management," Annotated Bibliography[John N. Warfield], August 1990 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - "Generic Systems Design & Integrative Management ," Annotated Bibliogrpahy John N. Warfield], August 1990 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - "The Great University, Original Seminar Poster & Handouts", 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - "Great University Seminar Series," Presented at George Mason University, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - "Great University Seminar Series," Presented at George Mason University., 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - "Generic Systems Deign &, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - "Strategies for Linking Producer & Users of the Technology in Ghana," [John N. Warfield], January 1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - , undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Integration Workshop on the Capacity Development and Utilization Program," [John N. Warfield, Roxana Cardenas], January 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - >"Council for Scientific & Industrial Research (C.S.I.R) WORKSHOPS," Ghana, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Council for Scientific & Industrial Research (C.S.I.R) Workshop Fax PaperS & Correspondence," Ghana, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Curriculum Workshop: Mathematics for Computer Science," [Roger Volkema], undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Working Papers, A-Z Reports," Ghana, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Final Report on the Workshop for Consensus Methodologies of Saudi Arabian National Center for Science & Technology (sancst)," [John N. Warfield], December 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Planning with the Virginia Division of Forestry," [William C. Wood, R.B. McDonald, A.N. Christakis], 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Structural Modeling in Corporate Environment," [Saunders, Cliff], 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Pathways for Forestry in Mississippi," [McDonald R.B., A.N. Christakis], 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "Gender Sensitivity & Report Writing Workshop," Funded by United Nations Development Program [Jeffrey, Carol], 1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - "Disarmament & Demobilization: Interactive Management Workshop," Monrovia, Liberia [Jeffrey, Carol], October 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - "Planning for an Industrial Training Board Team: IM Application," City University, London[F.R.Janes], 1989 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - "Understanding Defense System Acquisition Management," DSMC - CIM Background Papers", 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - "Special Seminar on Acquisition Management Alternatives," Virginia, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - "Redesigning the National Marine Fisheries Service for 1990's," [Keever], February 1986 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - "Risk Reduction / Management Workshop," DSMC, Virginia, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - "Technical Managers Advanced Workshop (T.M.A.W) Magazine", 1991 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C) Report on DoD Workshops in Concurrent Engineering," Virginia, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - "Human Service Needs: Setting Priorities," One Day Forum CIM, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - "Forum on the Future of Pediatric Nursing: Looking Forwards the Twenty First Century", May 1988 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - "Moving Toward the Effective Participation of Tribal Governments in the U.S. Federal System," [Cromer], June 29, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - "Designing a New Student Union Program for George Mason University," [Irene Cromer], 1988 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - "Employment Correspondence, Job Hunting, Positions Held by Cohn N. Warfield", 1984 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - "Burroughs Corporation Miscellaneous Materials Connected With Job, John N. Warfield", 1984-1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - "Mexico Workshop for Mexican Society for Cybernetics Correspondence & Memos", 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Office Chronology Notebook Correspondence & Memorabilia", 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Environmental Education & Information," John N. Warfield Contributed One Paper., 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Department of Conservation, California Correspondence," [John N. Warfield, Bala H. Banathy], 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "News Clippings at University of Virginia About (UVA) Scientific Research Committee", June 6, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Center for Participative System Design," A Proposal Prepared for Dean Gibson Which Predated Establishment of (C.I.M)", 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Center for Interactive Management (UVA) Newsletter", 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Center for Interactive Management Press Release & News Clippings on the Center," CIM, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Scholars Design Course, Class Notes, Term Papers & Correspondence," [Rodman], 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Center for Interactive Management (UVA) Correspondence Papers", 1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Walter Bogam Correspondence with John N. Warfield During Burroughs Corporation Phone Calls & Memos", 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "Virginia Division of Forestry," Correspondence Papers, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "Correspondence Related to I.S.M & Sabbatical Stay at C.I.M," Previous Employment of John N. Warfield, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - "Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future", 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - "U.S. Forest Service Papers, Correspondence Related to Work Done Through C.I.M.," (Univ of Virginia), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - "The Center for Interactive Management Seminar at Naval Surface Weapons Center," Dahlfren, Virginia, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - "Office Chronology Book & Miscellaneous Papers, Burroughs Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - "Office Chronology Book& Miscellaneous Papers, Burroughs Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - "Burroughs Corporation, Europe Trip Papers", 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - "University of Northern Iowa - Burroughs Corporation Contract & Correspondence Papers," [Robert Waller], March 1984 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - "IEEE SMC Conference, India Trip Papers," During Burroughs Corporation, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - "University of Northern Iowa - Burroughs Corporation Papers", 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - "Center for Interactive Management (C.I.M) Budgets Correspondence & Papers", 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - "Exxon Proposal on Graduate Engineering Education", June 1977 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - "Establishment of a Societal Systems Social Division, Proposal to Syracuse Research Corporation", July 1989 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - "Pacific Bell Proposal for a Seminar Presentation by John N. Warfield About I.S.M & G'S PC Version Software", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - "Nigeria Proposal About Applications of Interactive Management", 1992 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - "Transitive Interconnection of Transitive Structures," Proceedings of 1975 Pittsburgh Conference [John N. Warfield], April 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "Final Report on Complexity in Human Affairs," Research Report, Battelle Institute, January 2, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "Improving Behavior in Policy making," [John N. Warfield], August 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Methods of Idea Management," [John N. Warfield, Horst Geschka, Ronald Hamilton], August 1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Improving Group Problem-Solving," [John N. Warfield], 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "Profiles of Metapolicy," Proceedings IEEE 1975 Conference on Cybernetics & Society [John N. Warfield], September 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "Articles on Policy by Lasswell & Others," A Bibliography, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Societal Systems: Proof Reading Instructions,by John Wiley & Sons Publishers", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "Societal Systems: Battelle Consulting Agreement for Writing the Book by John N. Warfield", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "System,Planning,Policy & Complexity: A Methodological Perspective," [John N. Warfield], March 2, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - "Societal Systems: Bibliography for the Book," [John N. Warfield], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - "Societal Systems: File Copy of the Bound Book", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "Societal Systems: Editorial Notes on the Manuscript, Work Schedules", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "Societal Systems: Correspondence, Notes Work Record of Book in Progress", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - "Societal Systems: Copy Right Permission Obtained for Use in Book," [John N. Warfield], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "Societal Systems: Book Review", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - "Societal Systems: Notes & Correspondence During Preliminary Planning," [John N. Warfield], 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - "Implication Structures for System Interconnection Matrices," [John N. Warfield], January 1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "Compromising the Future: The Problem of Bounding Utility Measures for Technology Endeavors," [John N. Warfield], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - "Relations & Decisions Making," [John N. Warfield, Janet A. Fertig], April 1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - "Extending Interpretive Structural Modeling," [John N> Warfield], April 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - "The OFOP Method of System Design," [John N. Warfield], 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - "Crossing Theory & Hierarchy Mapping," [John N. Warfield], July 1977 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - "Societal Forces Influencing R & D in the 1980's," Outline of a Talk by John N. Warfield, June 1977 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - "Book Review: Redesigning the Future, A System Approach to Societal Problems," [Ackoff], October 1977 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - "Understanding the Delta Charts," [John N. Warfield], June 14, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - "Understanding the Delta Charts," [John N. Warfield], June 14, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - "A Descriptive Analysis of Environmental Education, Fourth Quarterly Report October 1978", undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - "Notes on Conceptual Sciences," [John N. Warfield], October 1978 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - >"Office of Environmental Education Contracts," [John N. Warfield, Bela Banathy], September 19, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - "Some Applications of Interpretive Structural Modeling," [John N. Warfield], November 6, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - "Options Profiles," Partial Draft [John N. Warfield], December 11, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 32)